https://devaland.com/privacy/

Privacy
Our Privacy Policy is clear:
We absolutely will not sell, share, rent or disclose any personal information about our customers. Period.
We value the privacy of our customers as our owns. We use strict security requirements and take all appropriate measures in order to protect the confidentiality of the materials and personal information that we receive from our customers.
We restrict access to personal information only to our employees who really need to know that information in order to operate our services.
Our staff members have signed confidentiality agreements so they are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.
We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet.
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
October 2020
M
T
W
T
F
S
S
1234
567891011
12131415161718
19202122232425
262728293031
What is LaTeX and Typesetting? LaTeX, pronounced lay-tech, is a document preparation system commonly used by scientists, engineers, mathematicians and other professionals. Unlike a typical word processor such as Microsoft Word, LaTeX uses a plain text markup language which is compiled into a PDF document using optimal typographical rules. This results in professional-looking documents that are of a different class to the output from a word processor - click here to see some examples.
LaTeX Typesetting Services
LaTeX Typesetting Prices
Samples
Careers / Freelancers
Privacy
Terms
Contact
© 2020 – Devaland. All rights reserved.
